<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Unabatedly Eigen</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Unabatedly Eigen</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A statistical approach to discerning adversarial attacks</title>
      <link>/blog/adversary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/adversary/</guid>
      <description>A neural network is a computer algorithm that uses calculus to, make predictions from a given set of parameters, either as a number(linear regression) or as a class(classification). One of the most useful cases of a Neural network is in image classification. In this project we use a statistical approach to identify the differences between white box adversarial attacks, black box adversarial attacks, and random noise. An adversarial attack consists of changing the pixels of input images to change a neural network’s prediction.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exhibition in The Fish Bowl</title>
      <link>/blog/presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/presentation/</guid>
      <description>Fishes Make Silly Pets A fish is an interesting choice for a pet. Given it&amp;rsquo;s incessant need for water, and inability to maneuver on the dry ground, you can&amp;rsquo;t play with it. Fish don&amp;rsquo;t have distinguishable emotions, or perhaps any emotions at all, so it can be difficult to attempt to project emotions upon them. Also, no cute girl is ever going to come up to you and ask if she can pet your fish, while walking your companion through the park.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Vestibule For Expansion</title>
      <link>/blog/first3weeks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/first3weeks/</guid>
      <description>A Vestibule For Expansion April 16th, 2018, A young bare faced boy jaunted into his new workplace. Greeted warmly, he proceeded to receive a tour of this strange new environment. After a brief overview of the facility, he was led to his new office. Yes, his very own office. With his own computer, and desk. This was a monumentally novel experience. To have ones own office was indeed strange, yet added only to the excitement of the experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Machine Learning Model</title>
      <link>/blog/2018-04-27-linkedin-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/2018-04-27-linkedin-post/</guid>
      <description>These last two weeks I&amp;rsquo;ve been extremely overwhelmed with my new internship. I showed up ready to use some of my powerful statistics and visualization skills, and within a few hours of playing with data realized that most of what I knew wasn&amp;rsquo;t going to be applicable to my work. As I scrambled to find solutions to my problems, and new methods to approach my task at hand, I very quickly realized that in order to succeed I was going to need to teach myself some machine learning skills.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>